Bryan Kowal

Glassboro, New Jersey, United States

badboybry9000@gmail.com

inkedin.com/in/bryan-kowal

856-906-4425

https://bryan-kowal.netlify.app

Summary

Full stack web app developer with experience developing apps within an Nx monorepo. Front-end experience is primarily with Angular and all the various technologies that would entail including TypeScript, RxJS, NgRx, HTML, and SASS. Back-end experience includes Laravel, PHP, and MySQL.

Believe it or not I actually enjoy writing unit tests using Jest and Cypress. I am also familiar with developing mobile apps with Ionic alongside web apps using the code sharing capabilities a monorepo affords.

I am currently interested in pursuing my career as a Web App Developer.

Previously developed .net desktop/console apps using C#, Crystal Reports, and SQL Server.

Additionally experienced using the Adobe Creative Suite and Microsoft Office Suite.

Experience

Web Application Developer

Household Metals, Inc.

Dec 2003 - Present (18 years 9 months +)

S Graphics / UI Designer

Drexel University
Sep 2001 - Nov 2003 (2 years 3 months)

🎎 Technical Support Agent

Drexel University Sep 2001 - Aug 2002 (1 year)

Education



Bachelor's degree

1998 - 2003

Skills

Angular • NgRx • Unit Testing • TypeScript • RxJS • Jest • Cypress • PHP • Laravel • MySQL